athletes face an uphill battle in the
Philippines the last decade has seen the
greatest number of Filipino Champions
leaving the country due to lack of
support it's no different in Esports a
tragedy especially in a country with
some of the best gamers in the region as
one of the youngest Insurance brand in
Asia FWD wanted to support the next
generation's Esports Heroes to capture
the toughest Market segment for
insurance introduced fwd's the gamer
Insurance the first Insurance designed
especially for gamers FWD studied then
covered the most common gamer health
risks costing less than the average
video game you can buy it online without
going AFK it even comes with in-game
freebies the gamer Insurance launched
during one of the biggest Esports events
in Asia and FWD became the first
Insurance brand in Asian Esports
supporting players during the biggest
fight of their career
[Music]
fwd's the gamer insurance